that your service
how can this be I thought you were dead
I'm sorry Reinhard after everything that
happened I needed time
Renard I must say you're looking quite
well this life must agree with you and
you are looking as lovely as ever
this is just like old times Reinhard the
old timers must stick together teach
these kids a thing or two just like old
times Fionna why not
things may change but you never do
Reinhard what should I focus on today
focus on offense drive your enemy back
with the blows from your flail
Reinhard what should I focus on today
your shield keep yourself from harm the
best [__] against our enemies
Reinhard what should I focus on today
protect your teammates make sure they do
not falter
Reinhard what should I focus on today
try to keep me out of trouble
Reinhard what should I focus on today no
lesson today show me what you have
learned
stay close to me of course how else can
i bail you out when you get into trouble
sure you don't want to sit this one out
Reinhart every time every time I say no
today it's no different
hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
of course here you go love Deva
hey was wondering if you'd sign
something for me it's again for a friend
Oh after this match is over right now
it's time to get serious
the destruction caused by the omnec
spear it reminds me of home things can
be destroyed but as long as the people
are strong they can always be rebuilt
you don't take a hint do you Reinhardt
and you don't know how to stay down when
you're beaten
ah you kids today with your techno music
you should enjoy the classics like
Hasselhoff I can't even take you
seriously right now
why not we need to find you some new
tombs what's wrong with the classics
I love Hasselhoff have you heard night
rocker
I not don't you think it's time you hung
it up you're not getting any younger
never I will fight to my last breath
Rinehart I don't approve of you dragging
that poor girl around on your adventures
Brigitta has made her choice I withheld
her at my side
Reinhart what are your plans for the
holidays I'll probably visit organs
family in Gothenburg like the last few
years
rinette why is your shield so important
to you it is a reminder of my duty
Reinhart I have allocated my learning
processes towards analyzing your combat
performance
what an odd compliment
Reinhardt you know I had a poster of you
on my wall when I was younger I remember
the poster my hair was amazing
Reinhardt are we still on for ice
fishing you're not still sir about last
year are you I'll show you I'll catch
twice as many as you this year
armor how positively medieval ever takes
that is a complement by lady
you always did take good care of my
armor just try to keep it in one piece
servants
hi sometimes wonder if all that Armour
slows your brain down yeah and I
sometimes wonder if your height is why
you're always in such a bad mood
hi sometimes wonder if all that Armour
slows your brain down could you say that
again sometimes it's hard to hear you
all the way down there
Reinhart least number of eliminations
buys the post-mission drinks Lou it
shows these kids how it's done
Rinehart least number of eliminations
buys the post-mission drinks agreed like
the best man win
house Brigitta doing keeping everything
in working order a night could not ask
for more from his choir
Reinhardt you'd better not be filling my
daughter's head with stories ah she
hardly listens to her anyways
you know tambien you would make an
excellent Santa Claus oh maybe this here
you can be the elf
I think Ingrid's been working on
something
huh Winston heats up to us to keep our
comrade safe I'll be right behind you
sir
Reinhardt you said you would arm-wrestle
me nervous nervous me
keep training and maybe someday you
could learn to handle a real weapon I
think I've got this old man finally I
beat ends a champion at arm wrestling
I heard it was your birthday old man so
I went easy on you
not strong enough
traitor
I slay dragons
that is today's lesson you still have
much to learn Squire
your seeds still need some work
when struck bricky dead I filled with
pride
your mother would approve her would be
proud
well done my diminutive Swedish friend
ha Gyung I will avenge you